Floor-Plan Studio. The library lists every property; the rail on the left is your review history, with the rent uplift for each.
Open the seeded property. The context bar keeps the numbers in view — nine hundred a week today, twelve-sixty proposed.
The plan is a live shape object, not a picture. Every room, wall, opening, and fixture is a real thing you can select — and every room shows its dimensions.
Delta view is a computed geometry diff against the original. Green added, red removed, amber modified.
You can edit directly. Rename the store to a study, make it habitable, and apply — it lands in under a second, validated, with no agent.
Or hand a change to the agent. Select the wall between the living area and the kitchen.
Describe the change in plain English: a servery window, and an island bench. Comments queue locally.
Send. The DeepSeek agent replies with typed geometry operations — never pixels — and the envelope can never grow.
The new version arrives live, with the servery window, the bench, and a fresh rent estimate.
The change register interleaves both authors — HUMAN and AGENT — and every line traces back to a geometry object. Export any version as a plan or a summary.
Select, edit or ask, done. One canvas, shared by you and the agent.