FLOOR-PLAN STUDIO — the plan library. 231 Peats Ferry Rd is seeded at v03, $1,260/wk. Any listing floor-plan image can be uploaded for AI vision ingestion.
The review. The plan is a live SVG shape object — every room and wall is a selectable node. Header chips carry the rent story: $900 baseline → $1,260/wk (+$360).
DELTA VS ORIGINAL — a computed geometry diff, not a drawing: red dashed = removed (garage, lounge, balcony), green = added (Bed 4, Bed 5, ensuites, robes), amber = modified.
Versions are immutable. v00 is the original 3-bed/1-bath plan. On the right: the change register — one git-style hunk per change, with rent impact and NSW advisory flags.
Selecting the STORE room, then shift-clicking the wall between living and kitchen. The red handles can trim a wall selection to the exact chunk where a window should go.
One comment covers both targets: store becomes a STUDY + a servery window in the selected wall section. Comments queue locally — nothing sends until you press send.
Sent to the agent (Pydantic AI on DeepSeek). It answers with TYPED GEOMETRY OPS — validated before they land. The building envelope can never grow; bad edits bounce back.
The new version arrives over SSE: the store is now a STUDY with a servery window, and the agent re-estimated the weekly rent live — the header chips update in place.
The new hunk joins the register — every +/− line traces to a geometry object, with NSW advisory flags. Any version exports as a styled PNG or SUMMARY.md.
Select → comment → send. The agent edits geometry, never pixels. github.com/nmp-dsci/floor-plan-reviewer